

# CONTACTS



+37068127238



arnoldasstrukcinskas@gmail.com



Kaunas



LinkedIn profile



My Projects



My Web Page

# **TECH STACK**

- Back-End: Java, Spring Boot, C++,
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JS
- Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Tools: Git, IntelliJ, CLion, Visual
- Additional: Azure cloud(basics), FTP(basics), Axure, AutoCad

# JOB EXPERIENCE

Pool technical specialist/lifeguard UAB "Eglės" sanatorium 2021-07 - 2024-06

Car fleet maintanance/manager Citybee, UAB "PrimeLeasing" 2021-04 - 2021-12

Physiotherapy UAB "Eglės" sanatorium 2018-07 - 2021-07

# **LANGUAGES**

- Lithuanian (Native)
- Russian (Near-native)
- English (B2 lygis)

# ARNOLDAS STRUKČINSKAS

Junior Back-End developer

## **ABOUT ME**

Programming has been my passion since adolescence. I am currently studying Software Systems at Vilnius College and actively deepening my knowledge. I have a strong work ethic, can work well in a team, and solve technical challenges independently.

# **EDUCATION**

## Software developer bachelor's degree

2024 - now

Vilnius University of Applied Sciences

## Sports physiotherapy master's degree

2019 - 2021

Lithuanian University of Health sciences

#### Physiotherapy bachelor's degree

2015 - 2019

Lithuanian University of Health sciences

# **PROJECTS**

#### 2D platformer game | Link

- Created with C++
- Graphical design made with SFML library
- 2D RPG type game

## BattleShips game | Link

- · Created using Java and Spring Boot
- Usual BattleShips game

# **COURSES**

# JAVA software development

Vilnius Coding School

## Java Programming Masterclass updated to Java 17

Udemy.com

135.5h

#### C# Basics for Beginners: Learn C# Fundamentals by Coding

Udemy.com

5.5h